<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Olokart Business</string>
    <string name="title_activity_home">HomeActivity</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="nav_header_title">Android Studio</string>
    <string name="nav_header_subtitle">android.studio@android.com</string>
    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

    <string name="menu_home">Home</string>
    <string name="google_maps_key">AIzaSyD5qHZ4_vugCBRgSmXK-hzdbaTl-xNXyA4</string>
    <string name="menu_gallery">Gallery</string>
    <string name="menu_slideshow">Slideshow</string>

    <string name="home_second">Home Second</string>
    <string name="title_activity_seller_home">SellerHomeActivity</string>
    <string name="title_home">Home</string>
    <string name="title_dashboard">Dashboard</string>
    <string name="title_notifications">Notifications</string>

    <string name="desclaimer">
In no event shall Company or any parties, organizations or entities associated with the corporate brand name us or otherwise, mentioned at this Website be liable for any damages whatsoever (including, without limitations, incidental and consequential damages, lost profits, or damage to computer hardware or loss of data information or business interruption) resulting from the use or inability to use the Website and the Website material, whether based on warranty, contract, tort, or any other legal theory, and whether or not, such organization or entities were advised of the possibility of such damages.</string>

    <string name="aboutus">OloKart lets you buy groceries from your local Kirana store, online!\n

To get home delivery of your favorite groceries simply:\n

* Choose your nearby grocery store\n

* Select from a wide variety of products including Dal, Atta, Oil, Ghee, Sugar, Noodles,
Soaps and Shampoos.\n

* Enjoy home delivery within 24 hours!\n
Shop anytime, anywhere from the comfort and convenience of your home and support your local kirana stores. Every OloKart order is fulfilled from a grocery store in your area!\n

What can you expect from OloKart? \n

* Everything on your Grocery Shopping List:\n
All your favorite grocery products from local products to national and international brands including Amul, Bisleri, Saffola, Cadbury, Horlicks, Surf Excel, Lifebuoy, Dettol, Vim, Bru, Red Label, Taj Mahal, Haldiram, Kellog’s, Aashirvaad, Tata Salt, Maggi and many more!\n

* Your Trusted, Neighborhood, Local Store Completely Online:\n
Simple choose your store, place your order and sit back! \n

* Great Offers:\n
Get great grocery deals including product discounts, exciting coupons, free home delivery* and more!\n

* Home Delivery:\n
Get door step delivery of your order within 24 hours!\n

* Fast Checkout:\n
Pay using Cash on Delivery, UPI, e-wallets and more!\n

Looking for a grocery store near you?\n
Trying to do some shopping from your nearby kirana?\n
Running out of rations/groceries?\n
Got a craving for chocolates, namkeen, Dairy Milk Silk?\n
Detergent running low?\n


Stocking up on pulses and chawal for the month?\n
Urgent Maggi stocking?\n
Shopping at your local kirana store for years but find online shopping more convenient? Just looking for some groceries online?\n
Looking for the convenience of Home Delivery?\n
Searching for household essentials?\n
Wish someone would deliver the groceries you want, from the store you want?\n

OloKart is the answer to all these questions and more. We would love to serve you \n

OLOKART BUSINESS\n

We are empowering our Partnered Kiranas with the Digital India and with the power of technology we are connecting Farmers with these outlets in order to benefit the farmers pricing issues in our country.\n

The Mission of the OLOKART is to empower the backbone of India i.e. farmers with power of technology  to connect them with direct consumers through small businesses.</string>
    <string-array name="spin_quant">
        <item> 5 </item>
        <item> 10 </item>
        <item> 20 </item>
        <item> 50 </item>
        <item> 100 </item>
        <item> 200 </item>
        <item> 500 </item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="spin_minim">
        <item> 500 </item>
        <item> 1000 </item>
        <item> 1500 </item>
        <item> 2000</item>
    </string-array>


    <string-array name="spin_dimen">
        <item>kg</item>
        <item>gm</item>
        <item>lt</item>
        <item>ml</item>
        <item>pc</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="spin_month">
        <item>Today</item>
        <item></item>
        <item>1lt</item>
        <item>1ml</item>
        <item>1mt</item>
        <item>1cm</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="spin_products">
        <item> Air freshners </item>
        <item> Baby products </item>
        <item> Bread and eggs </item>
        <item> Butter, Cheese and paneer </item>
        <item> Chicken meet and seafood </item>
        <item> Chips and namkeen </item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="spin_city">
        <item> Hanamkonda </item>
        <item> kazipet </item>
        <item> shyampet </item>
        <item> Fathimanagar </item>
        <item> Bollikunta </item>
        <item> Adalath </item>
        <item> Naimnagar </item>
        <!--        <item> Nakkalagutta </item>-->
        <!--        <item> Ambedkar </item>-->
        <!--        <item> Dighori </item>-->
        <!--        <item> Umred </item>-->
        <!--        <item> Burdi </item>-->
        <!--        <item> Narendra Nagar  </item>-->
        <!--        <item> SuyogNagar </item>-->
        <!--        <item> Sakkardara </item>-->
        <!--        <item> LaxmiNagar </item>-->
        <!--        <item> Bajaj </item>-->
    </string-array>
    <string name="title_activity_drawer">DrawerActivity</string>
    <string name="hello_world">Hello world!</string>
    <string name="date_label_set">Press the button to set the date</string>
    <string name="date_button_set">Set Date</string>
    <string name="date_view_set">The Date is: </string>
    <string name="date_selected"></string>


    <string-array name="titles">
        <item>Prakash</item>
        <item>Bhavin</item>
        <item>Chirag</item>
        <item>Yakub</item>
    </string-array>
    <string name="termsandconditions">The terms \"We\" / \"Us\" / \"Our\"/”Company” individually and collectively refer to digidine.in and the terms \"Visitor” ”User” refer to the users.\n  This page states the Terms and Conditions under which you (Visitor) may visit this website (“Website”).\n Please read this page carefully. If you do not accept the Terms and Conditions stated here, we would request you to exit this site.\n The business, any of its business divisions and / or its subsidiaries, associate companies or subsidiaries to subsidiaries or such other investment companies (in India or abroad) reserve their respective rights to revise these Terms and Conditions at any time by updating this posting.\n You should visit this page periodically to re-appraise yourself of the Terms and Conditions, because they are binding on all users of this Website.\n USE OF CONTENT All logos, brands, marks headings, labels, names, signatures, numerals, shapes or any combinations thereof, appearing in this site, except as otherwise noted, are properties either owned, or used under licence, by the business and / or its associate entities who feature on this Website.\n The use of these properties or any other content on this site, except as provided in these terms and conditions or in the site content, is strictly prohibited.  You may not sell or modify the content of this Website or reproduce, display, publicly perform, distribute, or otherwise use the materials in any way for any public or commercial purpose without the respective organisation’s or entity’s written permission. \n ACCEPTABLE WEBSITE USE (A)\n Security Rules Visitors are prohibited from violating or attempting to violate the security of the Web site, including, without limitation, (1) accessing data not intended for such user or logging into a server or account which the user is not authorised to access,\n (2) attempting to probe, scan or test the vulnerability of a system or network or to breach security or authentication measures without proper authorisation, \n(3) attempting to interfere with service to any user, host or network, including, without limitation, via means of submitting a virus or \"Trojan horse\" to the Website, overloading, \"flooding\", \"mail bombing\" or \"crashing\", or\n (4) sending unsolicited electronic mail, including promotions and/or advertising of products or services.\n Violations of system or network security may result in civil or criminal liability.\n The business and / or its associate entities will have the right to investigate occurrences that they suspect as involving such violations and will have the right to involve, and cooperate with, law enforcement authorities in prosecuting users who are involved in such violations.\n  Visitors may not use the Web Site in order to transmit, distribute, store or destroy material (a) that could constitute or encourage conduct that would be considered a criminal offence or violate any applicable law or regulation, \n(b) in a manner that will infringe the copyright, trademark, trade secret or other intellectual property rights of others or violate the privacy or publicity of other personal rights of others, or \n(c) that is libellous, defamatory, pornographic, profane, obscene, threatening, abusive or hateful.  INDEMNITY The User unilaterally agree to indemnify and hold harmless, without objection, the Company, its officers, directors, employees and agents from and against any claims, actions and/or demands and/or liabilities and/or losses and/or damages whatsoever arising from or resulting from their use of rentji.com or their breach of the terms .\n  LIABILITY User agrees that neither Company nor its group companies, directors, officers or employee shall be liable for any direct or/and indirect or/and incidental or/and special or/and consequential or/and exemplary damages, resulting from the use or/and the inability to use the service or/and for cost of procurement of substitute goods or/and services or resulting from any goods or/and data or/and information or/and services purchased or/and obtained or/and messages received or/and transactions entered into through or/and from the service or/and resulting from unauthorized access to or/and alteration of user\'s transmissions or/and data or/and arising from any other matter relating to the service, including but not limited to, damages for loss of profits or/and use or/and data or other intangible, even if Company has been advised of the possibility of such damages. \n User further agrees that Company shall not be liable for any damages arising from interruption, suspension or termination of service, including but not limited to direct or/and indirect or/and incidental or/and special consequential or/and exemplary damages, whether such interruption or/and suspension or/and termination was justified or not, negligent or intentional, inadvertent or advertent.\n  User agrees that Company shall not be responsible or liable to user, or anyone, for the statements or conduct of any third party of the service.\n In sum, in no event shall Company\'s total liability to the User for all damages or/and losses or/and causes of action exceed the amount paid by the User to Company, if any, that is related to the cause of action.</string>
    <string name="title_activity_home_pickup">HomePickup</string>
    <string name="tab_text_1">Tab 1</string>
    <string name="tab_text_2">Tab 2</string>
    <string name="title_activity_recent_deliv">RecentDeliv</string>
    <string name="title_activity_home_pick_options_tab">HomePickOptionsTab</string>
</resources>